[
  {
    "front": "gauche",
    "back": "左"
  },
  {
    "front": "droite",
    "back": "右"
  },
  {
    "front": "enfant",
    "back": "子"
  },
  {
    "front": "homme, masculin",
    "back": "男"
  },
  {
    "front": "femme, fille, féminin",
    "back": "女"
  },
  {
    "front": "voiture, véhicule",
    "back": "車"
  },
  {
    "front": "quoi, quel, combien",
    "back": "何"
  },
  {
    "front": "blanc",
    "back": "白"
  },
  {
    "front": "haut, cher",
    "back": "高"
  },
  {
    "front": "long, chef",
    "back": "長"
  }
]
